

# Danny Blackstock

dannyblackstock.com

❷ dannyblackstock@gmail.com

**6**04 936 6778

# profile

I am a multidisciplinary designer and senior student at Simon Fraser University's School of Interactive Art and Technology. I enjoy learning how and why people's everyday experiences can be affected by design, and I have a strong interest in user interface design, web development, and videography.

# technical skills

Proficient		Working knowledge	
Photoshop	Flash	PHP	Arduino
Illustrator	HTML + CSS	Javascript	Processing
Indesign	Git	MySQL	After Effects
Premiere	SketchUp	Python	

# work experience

**User Experience Designer / Developer** for Evident Point Software | 2013 Evident Point is a small software company developing e-Publishing software.

#### Roles

- Design user interfaces for an interactive e-book web application, as well as websites, Android, iOS, and Windows applications.
- Create sketches and mockups to communicate how these designs will work and look to clients and development team.
- Produce and implement designs and assets into websites and web applications using HTML, CSS, and SASS, and optimize assets for use in native tablet apps.
- Test and resolve minor bugs in a Javascript web application, while working in a Ruby on Rails environment.

#### Results

Designs implemented into a web application with thousands of users, as well as native iOS, Android, and Windows applications, and various websites. Communicated with clients successfully to fulfill their needs and requirements.

# community involvement

# **Graphic Designer** for Sense Tecnic Systems | 2013

Sense Tecnic is a software company developing tools for ubiquitous computing.

#### Roles

- Design a variety of icons and interface elements for a mobile web application, while being consistent with the client's branding.
- Create mockups to illustrate what the designs would look like to the client.
- Integrate them into the Kurugo mobile web application by generating assets and implementing them using CSS.
- Test the designs on various mobile devices.

## Results

Designs used in demo applications for the cities of Richmond and Surrey, BC.



# **community involvement** Technology Coordinator for Enactus Simon Fraser | 2012 - 2014

Enactus SFU is an organization that uses entrepreneurial projects to address the social, environmental, and economic needs in the community.

### Roles

- · Maintain and enhance the user experience of Enactus SFU's various websites, through interface design, as well as HTML, CSS, and WordPress customization.
- · Shoot, edit and compile video, images, and audio of Enactus events and causes.
- · Create motion graphics in After Effects to enhance the message of the videos.
- · Collaborate and communicate effectively with different teams in order to complete cohesive video projects for their needs.

### Results

Created a event commercial shown on national television, produced videos that were used in competitions with other university Enactus groups, as well as presentations to Simon Fraser University's faculty and students.

# Graphic Designer for MADRenegade | 2011 - 2012

MADrenegade, or Media Advertising and Design by Renegade, was a small creative organization run by Students in Free Enterprise SFU, now called Enactus SFU.

### Roles

- Conceptualize, sketch, and create logos for fellow SFU student projects.
- · Communicated with these students in order to produce and deliver work that is tailored for them and leaves them satisfied.

#### Results

Logo designs were used by senior business students in their academic projects.

#### awards

#### President's Honour Roll

Achieved a term GPA of 4.0 or above while enrolled in at least 12 units of classes.

### Seattle Design Charette Fall 2012

Part of the winning team of a three day spatial / architectural design competition.

# Simon Fraser University Summit Entrance Scholarship

Grade 12 average greater than 90%.

### Media Arts 12 Scholarship

Awarded for receiving the highest mark in the class.

### education

### Simon Fraser University | 2011-Present

School of Interactive Arts & Technology. This program focuses on combining science, art, and technology into the creation of digital and physical systems and effective design.

#### i also enjoy

Epic hiking adventures, playing drums, cars, skiing, tennis, and rock music (eg. The Strokes, Foals, Tokyo Police Club).